<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="Text">

    </string-array>
    <string-array name="Task">
        <item>Run around the room imitating a gorilla or a monkey if not then drink.</item>
        <item>Using a random object, demonstrate how to give a BLOWJOB or finish your drink.</item>
        <item>Pick another player.Together, find a stranger and each of you tell the stranger a joke. Let them be the judge on whose joke was funnier. The loser drinks twice. </item>
        <item>Dance hula hooping for 30 seconds or drink.</item>
        <item>Pour water on your pants so it looks like you pissed yourself. Let the group post it on Instagram with a сaption of their choosing. Do this, take two shots, or quit playing.</item>

        <item>Kiss the player of your choice on the forehead,then sniff it or drink four times.</item>

        <item>Drink if youve ever written without your hands.</item>
         <item>The title of the film "Titanic" shows without words. The first one to guess decides who gets four sips. If no one gets it right, you drink.</item>
        <item>You tell the most shameful story or you drink twice.</item>
        <item>Eat whatever other players make or drink.</item>
        <item>Eat something very spicy or drink.</item>
        <item>Sing PIKOTARO - PPAP or drink.</item>
        <item>Dance striptease to Isyan Tetick - Patlamaya Devam or drink.</item>
        <item>Swap some clothes with a player of your choice or drink.</item>
        <item>Make a group chat with all the people youve ever had sex with saying: "Hoping all my sexual partners could connect :3" finish your drink, or quit playing.</item>
        <item>Pick someone whos not a player and dance a romantic dance with them or drink.</item>
        <item>Wear socks for three rounds or drink.</item>
         <item>Wear your pants backwards for three rounds or drink.</item>
        <item>Let the player across the room make-up or drink.</item>
        <item>Playing scissors rock paper with the player across from who lost and drinks.</item>
        <item>Break an egg on your head or drink.</item>
        <item>Eat something without using your hands or drink.</item>
        <item>Make a shirt / skirt out of a garbage bag and wear it for the next two rounds or drink.</item>
        <item>Eat a spoon of mustard or drink.</item>
        <item>Break up with your girlfriend / boyfriend or drink (ratio more expensive).</item>
        <item>Do a belly dance, take a video and upload it to Instagram or drink.</item>

         <item>Call your parents and tell them theyre grounded for a week or drink.</item>
        <item>Put the ice in your shirt or your underwear until it melts or you drink.</item>
        <item>Try licking your elbow while you sing a song or drink.</item>
        <item>Call your ex and try to get back in the XD relationship better drink.</item>
        <item>Massage someone here or drink.</item>
        <item>Put your bad photo on social media. Let other people choose it or drink it.</item>
        <item>Say «MonkeySlut» at the end of each of your and others lines, until your turn or drink.</item>
        <item>Open up any social media outlet, log on to the first person you see, and type on every post or drink.</item>
        <item>Close your eyes and let the other participants put in your mouth any food from the fridge they choose ,or drink.</item>
        <item>Let each player choose one word, and then you write them and publish them on social media or drink them twice.</item>
         <item>Give your phone to the person in front of you and have him post whatever he wants on your social media accounts or drink.</item>
        <item>Call your friend/girlfriend and tell them youre gay/lesbian or drink.</item>
        <item>Call and tell your friend/girlfriend or drink.></item>
        <item>Dial a random number and try to sell the vibrator or drink. If no one answers, the task is not counted.</item>
        <item>Sit in the closet or under the table until its your turn again or drink.</item>
        <item>Tap-dance while everyones filming or drinking.</item>
        <item>Draw a moustache on your face with whatever you want. Dont erase it for the rest of the game or drink it.</item>
        <item>Show your favorite sex pose without photos or videos or drink.</item>
        <item>Show a porn actor/actress without a word the one who guesses who chooses whom to drink, if no one guesses then drink.</item>
        <item>Take off your top clothes and pretend youre a bodybuilder Pose like a bodybuilder. Do 10 poses or drink.</item>
         <item>Stand in a cancer pose on the ground and shake your ass on video or drink.</item>
        <item>Players set you up on social media at their discretion or drink twice.</item>
        <item>Fill your mouth with food and try whistling or drinking.</item>
        <item>Make clothes out of toilet paper and upload photos to social media or drink.</item>
        <item>You call someone you like and tell them you love them or drink them.</item>
        <item>Smell the armpits on the right of the sitting player or drink.</item>
        <item>Theyll tie your eyes and put you in front of the fridge with a finger and eat or drink.</item>
        <item>Ask the neighbors for toilet paper or drink.</item>

        <item>Bite an onion like an apple if you dont have onions.</item>
         <item>Blindfolded, you can guess who hit you in the ass and continue until you know. Or you can just drink.</item>
        <item>Each of the players draws a tattoo of your body or drinks.</item>
        <item>They draw you a  unibrow, take a picture and throw it on the social network or drink.</item>
        <item>You masage any players feet or you drink.</item>
        <item>Youre gonna miss every players kiss if they say yes, then kiss them if they say no, then drink.</item>
        <item>You give a love bite vacuum a blow, you take a picture, and you throw it on the social media, and the players come up with a signature or a drink.</item>
        <item>Make a love bite on your arm or drink.</item>
        <item>You get a hickey on your cheek or you drink.</item>
        <item>Show your blow job on a banana or drink.</item>
        <item>Throw money to charity or drink.</item>
         <item>Spray perfume or deodorant in your mouth or drink.</item>
        <item>You sing a song that the players wish on or drink to you.</item>
        <item>You say the main downside to each player or you drink.</item>
        <item>Lick the soap or drink.</item>
</string-array>
</resources>